<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Resume application</string>

    <!-- project names -->
    <string name="project_1_name">WeatherStation(P1.1)</string>
    <string name="project_2_name">Autonomously Guided Robot(P1.2)</string>
    <string name="project_3_name">Trainstation Schedule Planner (P1.3)</string>
    <string name="project_4_name">Magic Arcade (P1.4)</string>
    <string name="project_5_name">Resume app (P1.4)</string>

    <!-- project descriptions -->
    <string name="project_1_Description">
        My first project was using weather data and a pre-made User Interface to show current relevant weather data.
    </string>

    <string name="project_2_Description">
        This project I along with some other students was tasked to develop an autonomously driving robot for a goat farmer.
    </string>

    <string name="project_3_Description">
        The project where the goal was to develop a schedule planner for a train station alongside a
        simulation to show the planning.
    </string>

    <string name="project_4_description">
        this project me and my team of developers were tasked with developing an attraction for the
        fictitious theme park "Essteling".
    </string>

    <string name="project_5_Description">
        A smaller sized project where the goal was to develop an app that could function as a resume.
    </string>

    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>


    <string name="personalDescription">I am David van der Veer, A first years software developer, I study at Avans University in Breda.
        \nDuring my time as a software developer I have taken part in multiple projects which I wil show (through an image) and talk about in this application.
        \nI like spending my free time comming up with projects of my own and making them a reality, I haven't yet finished my current personal project which is why its not included in this application.
    </string>

    <string name="buttonText">Project list</string>

    <string name="detailedExplanation">
        During the fist period of my first year I worked on creating algorithms to calculate and process weather data.
        I did this together with a couple fellow first years and the help of our senior developers.
        \nI personally worked on showing relevant data on the GUI we were handed by our teachers,
        calculating the median values for all weather data, and converting the raw measurements into readable (european) values.
    </string>

    <string name="detailedExplanationP2">
        During the second period of my first year our assignment was to develop an Autonomously Driving Robot.
        We got the specifications of this project later on in the period through customer conversations,
        the customer told us he was a goat farmer looking to ease the process of feeding his animals.
        \nMy personal work on this project involved working on the structure of the code, making sure the code
        that was written was reliable and proper code, and adding the funtionality for the ultrasonic scanner.
    </string>
    <string name="detailedExplanationP3">
        During the third period of my first year we were tasked with developing a GUI that functioned
        as a planner for a train station and visualising this schedule through a basic 2D simulation
        (although our group opted for a top-down perspective).
        \nThis period I personally worked on the C(reate).R(ead).U(pdate).D(elete) functions for all schedule items,
        for example: trains, and platforms. I also implemented a visual clock for the simulation (both digital and analogue),
        and I worked on a slider that either sped up time in the simulation or slowed it down depending on its positions.
    </string>
    <string name="detailedExplanationP4">
        During the fourth period of my first year me and my team of developers were tasked with creating a fun new
        attraction for the theme park Essteling. this period I assumed the role of team leader and focussed on
        growing within this role. However I did also work on the project itself.
        \nMy main jobs during this project was designing. I was designed and drew the controller that we made,
        I drew the circuit diagram, and I solderd all of the components together.
    </string>
    <string name="detailedExplanationP5">
        The final project I worked on during my first year was a resume application. the goal here was to
        create an app that could be shown to future potential employers to show my capabilities concerning
        software development.
        \nPersonally I was very proud of my accomplishments surrounding this application as I didnt really
        get the chance to work on android development during the Magic arcade development so I was slightly
        inexperienced. Nevertheless I personally think that this application turned out really well, even working on
        any size device and having backwards compatibility up to android 6.0.

    </string>
</resources>